Pocket camera using the link in my bio.
Price review, I share my kitchen with two other doctors and so four nights I paid 109 pounds.
We're having a repressed coffee outside our first day of induction.
Yes, vibes actually.
It feels like first day of school doesn't it?
It does, but last week I'm going to the village.
He's going to where we were doing our first year basically.
Which we don't think.
The unnamed city.
Unnamed city?
Well, village.
So I'm glad to be in the, what do you call it?
You know when a city is like a raw tag.
It's like...
I'm going to sell my...
Felicity is russum.
Like the fellow?
Yeah, developed by like they say, um, like, much of a cosmopolitan.
That's a bit of a politician.
Sounds like that.
It's like, um...
Down village?
I am back in the thing you say.
Oh, civilization!
Why did you...
I think it's the thing that's hitting the figure out.
It's the word.
For the first one minute.
Yeah, I feel like I'm back in civilization.
So I'm super happy with it.
It's nice.
It's nice views from the hospital.
We just had our ID cards.
You know how I'm doing?
I'll probably buy.
We're just having a break.
We're not doing anything today.
Until the first quarter.
Yeah, we're just going to have the induction.
Black Wednesday.
That's beautiful.
Wait, what's black Wednesday?
So every year, when there's new people rotating,
whether it's at once, if it's two IMTs, everyone,
it's called black Wednesday.
Because all the teams change across the whole country.
And it's the worst day for patients to get to the better.
Oh, yeah.
Because everything is busy.
There's no coordinates.
No one knows each other.
No one knows the...
I work on orthopedics.
I have no idea what the word is.
I don't even know the name of the word.
So, yeah, it is what they're doing.
Oh, okay. I think I'll try to do it.
Yeah, so black Wednesday.
It's quite sunny for a black Wednesday.
It is.
It's such a lovely day.
I'm doing okay.
Time-lapsey thing now.
She's a checker.
She's a lot.
So much.
Let's go in.
I'm sorry.
I'm pretty stuck with that.
I'm a medication.
So we're good folks.
By the evening, we're good folks.
We just had some lunch.
Now we're chilling outside
whilst waiting for our induction to start.
It's the same user they bought last word you
had for Alec.
It's not even though it is.
Yay!
We're done for the day.
I had such a good day.
This was such a good day.
Honestly, I'm so happy.
Compared to what I experienced last year
on my first day as a doctor.
It's crazy how different I feel right now.
Obviously it's also because I'm
I did not really prefer the place
that I was working in last year.
And you know, everyone was a lot more.
Now that I actually feel closer to home
because this town is a lot closer to home for me.
And I met the team.
Everyone's so nice.
I don't know.
It feels good.
Life is looking up.
I know it's crazy how there are more junior doctors than me
working on that ward.
I'm so used to being the most junior doctor.
Now that I'm not a baby doctor anymore
I have doctors that are more junior than me.
It feels like I'm very experienced, which I am.
Not very, but like I feel a lot more confident
compared to last year and more comfortable.
I'm a good doctor.
So yeah it's crazy how much I feel like I've grown.
I finished my week of working at this new hospital and came to the end of this
four-day rental in this accommodation because I was only staying here
temporarily whilst waiting for my new house to be ready and I just got the call.
What time we ate and to collect those keys tomorrow?
We're just around 1 o'clock?
Yes, exactly.
You don't get that 10 key room, it's 10 to cross, okay?
Okay, lovely. Thank you, bye.
So tomorrow I will be moving to my very first own place ever.
I never lived alone in my life, so I'm excited.
I feel like a proper adult, you know?
Please God, don't let me need a hospital accommodation state ever again in my life.
Obviously, never say never, you know?
If I need to, I will happily, not happily,
but I will be back.
I am hoping my life and hospital accommodation has come to an end now.
It's my sister's birthday celebration tomorrow.
If he feels good, that I don't need to miss my family and friends,
birthdays and special days anymore because I don't live too far anymore.
But that's the thing, like, as a doctor, especially during training.
You can go any part of the country, they can send you anywhere.
And if you want to continue training, you just have to stick it out.
Doctors don't have much location freedom and me realizing how important it is for me.
Made me reconsider my career choices.
No, yeah.